<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kevin Ta on kev-in-ta.github.io</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Kevin Ta on kev-in-ta.github.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kev-in-ta.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UniCal: Unified Neural Sensor Calibration</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/eccv2024-waabi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/eccv2024-waabi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>TIFF 2024 Nano-Reviews</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/tiff-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/tiff-2024/</guid><description>&lt;p>In my second year in Toronto, I got to experience TIFF again, an annual event that I had no inkling of before I moved here. The arts and culture scene in Toronto is truly spectacular and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got to experience two films, both of which I loved. Here are my micro-reviews for them!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="love-in-the-big-city">Love in the Big City&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt33022813/">IMDb&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/love_in_the_big_city_2024">Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Love in the Big City—as the move is aptly named—is a sentimental journey spanning thirteen years, following the rarely-featured platonic friendship through highly contemporary struggles. Powered by the leads&amp;rsquo; captivating chemistry, the film charms you as you’re whisked along two friends’ lives at breakneck pace. Despite the movie’s rough comedic whiplash, the story broaches its sensitive topics seriously, not shying away from its many painful and touching moments. ★★★★&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MUSES: The Multi-Sensor Semantic Perception Dataset for Driving under Uncertainty</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/eccv2024-cvl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/eccv2024-cvl/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Canadian News &amp; Social Media Monopolies</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/canadian-news/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/canadian-news/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey, have you noticed? &lt;a href="https://thetyee.ca/Opinion/2023/07/14/Meta-Blocked-Tyee-Journalism-Online-News-Act-Readers-Sharing/">News is hard to find these days on social media&lt;/a>&lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, not in small part because &lt;a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20231118193230/https://about.fb.com/news/2023/06/changes-to-news-availability-on-our-platforms-in-canada/">Meta decided to remove the presence of news organisations&lt;/a> in response to &lt;a href="https://www.justice.gc.ca/eng/csj-sjc/pl/charter-charte/c18_1.html">Bill C-18&lt;/a>. This bill aims to target the trillion dollar companies controlling the way we consume media in hopes of compensating Canadian news organisations. For companies who rely on, exploit, and control the modern distribution of news, it seems par for the course to utilise their monopoly position to try and force governments and the fourth estate to back down.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What's in your Media Diet?</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/media-diet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/media-diet/</guid><description>&lt;p>With the arrival of the digital age, we were promised unparalleled access to information and knowledge. Now that we are solidly &lt;a href="https://home.cern/science/computing/birth-web/short-history-web">three decades&lt;/a> into the world wide experiment that is the internet, it’s as good a time as any to interrogate how we get access to information, what kind of risks exist in our current media landscape, and how we can take control to critically examine the information that we consume.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>UncLe-SLAM: Uncertainty Learning for Dense Neural SLAM</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/iccvw2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/iccvw2023/</guid><description/></item><item><title>L2E: Lasers to Events for 6-DoF Extrinsic Calibration of Lidars and Event Cameras</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/icra2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/icra2023/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Fuelathons Addendum: Research Notes</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/fuelathons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/fuelathons/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Let&amp;rsquo;s look at a brief and very incomplete history of fuelathons!&lt;/strong> I wanted to make a more detailed piece about fuelathons in general as a companion post to my reflection on the &lt;a href="https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/sae-supermileage">SAE Supermileage competition&lt;/a>. Unfortunately, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a lot of historical record keeping over time, leaving a patchy network of details along the way. I wanted to share some of what I could find. (which is by no means exhaustive!)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SAE Supermileage: An Enduring Technical Challenge</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/sae-supermileage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/sae-supermileage/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>How far can you go on a litre of gasoline?&lt;/strong> After 43 years, the SAE Supermileage Competition came to a close in June 2022. To hear the end of a program that shaped much of my undergraduate experience left me reminiscing—of late nights hacking together prototype vehicles with fellow students all enchanted by the madness of collegiate engineering competitions. I was supposed to compete in 2020 as team captain of the &lt;a href="https://www.supermileage.ca/">UBC Supermileage team&lt;/a>, but lost the opportunity due to the pandemic. Now, a year after the last SAE Supermileage Competition, I wanted to dive in and share a brief and incomplete look at some of the stuff that made SAE Supermileage what it was.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Studying Abroad in a Pandemic</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/abroad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/abroad/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Deciding to do a master’s is both easy and hard.&lt;/strong> There’s a familiarity in pursuing further education when you’ve done the thirteen or so years of mandatory schooling and four more years for a bachelor’s (or six like me if you took your time). It’s easy to romanticize the pursuit of knowledge. On the other hand, you don&amp;rsquo;t make much (if any) money doing a master&amp;rsquo;s and many of the quirks of academia are genuinely bizarre. So what was it like to go to grad school? Let me share with you my experiences over the past 2 years in Switzerland.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ATTENTIV: Instrumented Peripheral Catheter for the Detection of Catheter Dislodgement in IV Infiltration</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2022/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Offline and Real-Time Implementation of a Terrain Classification Pipeline for Pushrim-Activated Power-Assisted Wheelchairs</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2021/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Offline and Real-Time Implementation of a Personalized Wheelchair User Intention Detection Pipeline: A Case Study</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/roman2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/roman2021/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Development of A Learning-Based Terrain Classification Framework for Pushrim-Activated Power-Assisted Wheelchairs</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/publications/embc2020/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>