<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Toronto on kev-in-ta.github.io</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/tags/toronto/</link><description>Recent content in Toronto on kev-in-ta.github.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kev-in-ta.github.io/tags/toronto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hot Docs 2025 Nano-Reviews</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/hotdocs-2025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/hotdocs-2025/</guid><description>&lt;p>I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m just drawn to films / documentaries centred around queerness, but here I am watching two more documentaries about the struggle for rights and freedoms. Here are my 2025 Hot Docs nano-reviews:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="parade-queer-acts-of-love--resistance-">Parade: Queer Acts of Love &amp;amp; Resistance 🇨🇦&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt36402660/">IMDb&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/parade_queer_acts_of_love_and_resistance">Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://www.nfb.ca/film/parade/">NFB&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>How did we get here? Parade covers some of the most poignant snapshots of queer expression and queer resistance in Canadian history. Glimpses into each era, a vignette of heroes in the storied history of the pursuit of liberation. The triumphs, the fights, and successes… And the struggle, the villains, and systems that oppress. Seeing the struggle in the same streets I walk on today, but from 70 years ago, is a stark reminder of how precarious the steps that were taken, how the struggle continues today. Informative and impressive in breadth, my core complaint is that each story deserves to be told in even more depth. ★★★&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>TIFF 2024 Nano-Reviews</title><link>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/tiff-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kev-in-ta.github.io/posts/tiff-2024/</guid><description>&lt;p>In my second year in Toronto, I got to experience TIFF again, an annual event that I had no inkling of before I moved here. The arts and culture scene in Toronto is truly spectacular and I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got to experience two films, both of which I loved. Here are my micro-reviews for them!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="love-in-the-big-city">Love in the Big City&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt33022813/">IMDb&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/love_in_the_big_city_2024">Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Love in the Big City—as the move is aptly named—is a sentimental journey spanning thirteen years, following the rarely-featured platonic friendship through highly contemporary struggles. Powered by the leads&amp;rsquo; captivating chemistry, the film charms you as you’re whisked along two friends’ lives at breakneck pace. Despite the movie’s rough comedic whiplash, the story broaches its sensitive topics seriously, not shying away from its many painful and touching moments. ★★★★&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>